[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The following countries have a border with India to the North West: ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "Afganistan"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "Shrilanka"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "China"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "Bhutan"}
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "The population of India according to the Census of 2001 is: ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "9,038 Million"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "1,028 Million"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "1,052 Million"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "1.074 Million"}
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "The contribution of agriculture to the GDP of India is roughly: ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "30%"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "33%"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "40%"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "45%"}
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "The following is a true statement in 2011: ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "India comprises of  28 states and 6 Union Territories"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "India comprises of 28 states and 5 Union Territories"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "India comprises of 28 states and 7 Union Territories"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "Indian comprises of 28 states and 8 Union Territories"}
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The constitution of India was adopted on : ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "1947"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "1948"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "1949"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "1950"}
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The National Fruit of India is the ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "Mango"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "Lotus Fruit"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "Gauva"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "Papaya"}
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "The National Tree of India is the: ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "Neem Tree"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "Lotus Tree"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "Banyan Tree"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "Mango Tree"}
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "The National Animal of India is the : ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "Tiger"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "Lion"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "Peacock"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "Leopard"}
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The song Vande Mantaram was composed by: ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "Rabindranath Tagore"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "Bankimchandra Chatterji"}
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "The song Jana-gana-Mana was originally composed in: ", 
        "options": [
            {"key": "a", "value": "Bengali"},
            {"key": "b", "value": "Hindi"},
            {"key": "c", "value": "Urdu"},
            {"key": "d", "value": "Sanskrit"}
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    }
]